{
 "data": [
        {
            "question": "At the sight of the orphan, she felt ___ rise in her heart.",
            "a": "a mother",
            "b": "mother",
            "c": "the mother",
            "d": "mothers",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "\n- The: used to show that you are talking about a particular thing or person that has already been mentioned, is already known about, or is the only one\n - One person there's only a mother\n",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "17"
        },
        {
            "question": "___ in the hand is worth two in the bush.",
            "a": "Bird",
            "b": "Birds",
            "c": "The bird",
            "d": "A bird",
            "answer": "4",
            "explain": "\n- \" A\" in this case meas \"one\"",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "17"
        },
        {
            "question": "My uncle comes here twice ___ week.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "in",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "by",
            "answer": "1",
            "explain": "\n- Twice a week= one week he come two times",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "17"
        },
        {
            "question": "Two of _________ seldom agree.",
            "a": "trade",
            "b": "a trade",
            "c": "the trade",
            "d": "trades",
            "answer": "2",
            "explain": "\n- Trade= an exchange of things\n- Two of a trade: two sides in an exchange of something",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "17"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is ___ in the back room of my house.",
            "a": "a picture",
            "b": "the another picture",
            "c": "my picture",
            "d": "more two pictures",
            "answer": "1",
            "explain": "\n- A: used to show that you are referring to a general type of person or thing and not a specific person or thing\n- This case, speakers only mentions a picture in general",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "17"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is your nationality? \" I am ___.\"",
            "a": "America",
            "b": "an American",
            "c": "Americans",
            "d": "the American",
            "answer": "2",
            "explain": "\n- A/an: used to show that you are referring to a general type of person or thing and not a specific person or thing",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "17"
        },
        {
            "question": " How did you pay the workers?  \" As a rule, they were paid ___.\"",
            "a": "by a hour",
            "b": "by an hour",
            "c": "by the hour",
            "d": "by hours",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "\n- Pay/charge by the hour (=pay or charge someone according to the number of hours it takes to do something)",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "17"
        },
        {
            "question": " Did you see a channel?  \" Yes, I've been to ___ Channel.\"",
            "a": "English",
            "b": "an English",
            "c": "the English",
            "d": "England",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "\n- Some places and countries, and all rivers and oceans, have the as part of their name\n",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "17"
        },
        {
            "question": " Did Miss Wang enjoy her trip on the ocean liner? \" No, she stayed in her cabin while the ship was ____\"",
            "a": "over the sea",
            "b": "in the sea",
            "c": "to sea",
            "d": "at sea",
            "answer": "4",
            "explain": "\n- Talking about time: Use at with holiday periods, meaning the few days around the holiday",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "17"
        },
        {
            "question": "I bought a pair of shoes ___.",
            "a": "at the half price",
            "b": "half at the price",
            "c": "at half the price",
            "d": "the half at price",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "\n- half the price/size/length etc",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "17"
        },
        {
            "question": " Did Sylvia fly across the Caspian Sea? \" No, she crossed both ways by ___.\"",
            "a": "a ship",
            "b": "the ship",
            "c": "ships",
            "d": "ship",
            "answer": "4",
            "explain": "\n- Do not use article in certain phrases made up of a preposition + noun:  on foot, at school, from top to bottom, at home, in bed, by train, by car, in debt, in hand, on earth, at noon, on board, in jest, at best, at worst etc\n",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "17"
        },
        {
            "question": "The chance to enter ___ came and she took it.",
            "a": "college",
            "b": "for college",
            "c": "in college",
            "d": "to college",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "\n- Enter in/into\n- - Do not use article in certain phrases made up of a preposition + noun:  on foot, at school, from top to bottom, at home, in bed, by train, by car, in debt, in hand, on earth, at noon, on board, in jest, at best, at worst etc\n",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "17"
        }
    ] 
}